<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Kustosz</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Kustosz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.kustosz.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kustosz 23.04.0</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-23.04.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-23.04.0/</guid><description>I’m happy to announce immediate availability of Kustosz 23.04.0.
This is maintenance update that brings latest ecosystem improvements to Kustosz users.
Kustosz has been verified against Django 4.2. This is newest LTS release that will be supported until April 2026, providing us with stable and safe foundation for years to come. One of notable improvements, included in Django 4.0, is native Redis cache backend.
We have also verified our codebase against Python 3.</description></item><item><title>Kustosz 22.08.0</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.08.0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.08.0/</guid><description>I’m happy to announce immediate availability of Kustosz 22.08.0.
This is small release that introduces one new feature - OPML export.
Kustosz promises you control over your data, and we are serious about this promise. It also means that it should be easy to move away from Kustosz, if you decide it&amp;rsquo;s not for you or you want to try out another tool. With OPML export, this is easier than ever.</description></item><item><title>Kustosz 22.07.0</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.07.0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.07.0/</guid><description>I’m happy to announce immediate availability of Kustosz 22.07.0.
The main feature of this release is content autodetection.
In previous releases, adding new content to Kustosz was a little hard. If you have found an interesting site that you wanted to subscribe to, you needed to find full URL of RSS / Atom feed. In many cases, that required checking HTML code of the page, which is especially hard to do on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Kustosz 22.06.0</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.06.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/kustosz-22.06.0/</guid><description>I’m happy to announce immediate availability of Kustosz 22.06.0.
This release is all about making Kustosz easier to try and install.
Container will automatically create new web user during start up. Now you can start the container with command below and immediately open localhost:8000/ui/ in the browser.
docker run -p 127.0.0.1:8000:8000 quay.io/kustosz/app Use KUSTOSZ_USERNAME and KUSTOSZ_PASSWORD to set username and password. When these variables are missing, user admin with random password will be created.</description></item><item><title>Announcing Kustosz</title><link>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/announcing-kustosz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kustosz.org/blog/announcing-kustosz/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce Kustosz, a new feed reader that aims to help you focus on worthwhile content.
These days, many open source RSS readers still try to fill the void left out by Google Reader - their main goal is to provide familiar visuals and user experience. Meanwhile, proprietary feed readers incorporate machine learning techniques to guide you through the vast ocean of content and try to &amp;ldquo;relieve&amp;rdquo; you from the burden of &amp;ldquo;reading everything&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>